-=北理FTP联盟字幕组=-
作品  本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=BiTUNiON SuBTiTLe GROUP=-
翻译：413413    校对：泠风紊雨
你死定了，臭婊子！
You're dead, bitch!
你他妈的看什么？
What the hell you lookin' at?
真他妈见鬼!
Fuckin' hell.
看来你今天很不走运啊，美女
Looks like you are shit outta luck, beautiful.
让我帮你来个剖腹产
Now i'm gonna give you your c-section.
你个婊子养的...
You son of a bi...
吃你的胡萝卜吧
eat your vegetables.
她在这边儿！
She's in here!
快点！
Come on!
她在哪？
Where is she?
她在那儿！
There she is!
- 快离开这儿！  - 那边儿！
- Get out of here! - Over there!
快杀了她！
Kill her on sight!
谁他妈的在那边？
Who the fuck is that?
那个女的跑哪去了？
Where the hell is the girl?
∮我畏惧，我畏惧，我畏惧∮
## I'm afraid, i'm afraid, i'm afraid ##
∮幽魂∮
## of ghosts ##
∮如果你∮
## if you have ##
干掉他！
get him!
∮我无意凝视∮
## I don't mean to stare ##
∮我不必养育∮
## we don't have to breed ##
∮我们可以盖间草房  我们可以种棵小树∮
## we can plant a house we can build a tree ##
∮我甚至都不在乎  “在那里一切都有”∮
## i don't even care, "we could have all three" ##
见鬼！  ∮她说过∮
- jesus! - ## She said ##
∮她说过∮
## she said ##
∮她说过，她说过∮
## she said ## ## she said ##
## she said, she said ##
∮她说过∮
## she said ##
哦，天呐，该死的！  ∮她说过∮
- oh, god! Fuck! - ## She said ##
∮她说过∮
## she said ##
∮她说过，她说过∮
## she said, she said ##
加油，用力，用力！
come on, push. Push!
我的手！
My hand!
- 你知道我讨厌什么吗？  - 不知道
- Do you know what i hate? - No.
我讨厌那些四十多岁的老男人  还留着马尾辫
I hate these 40-year-old jack-holes wearing ponytails.
- 马尾辫不会让你看上去时髦...  - 快点
- That ponytail doesn't make you look hip... - come on.
...年轻，或者很酷
...young, or cool.
好了，快出来了 再加把力
Ok, it's comin'. Come on.
再使劲来一次
Give me one big push.
∮她说过，她说过∮
## She said, she said ##
## she said, she said ##
∮她说过∮
## she said ##
你他妈的干什么吗？
what the fuck?
我流血了，快不行了
I'm bleedin'. I'm bleedin' out.
别乱动  不要干扰我瞄准
Quit squirming, you're ruining my shot.
什么烂东西
What a piece of crap.
我们得离开这里
We're outta here.
很抱歉这么粗鲁的搬动你
Sorry about the messy delivery, mom.
得安静下来
We need quiet.
给孩子点喝的
Give junior something to drink.
好极了，大英雄 棒极了
Bravo, mr. Hero. Bravo.
你们为什么要杀这个女人？
Why you tryin' to kill this woman?
很好笑吗？
Something funny?
哦，我只是突然想起了一首打油诗
Oh, i was just remembering a limerick.
“曾经有一个很能生的女人...”
Well, "there once was a woman who was quite begat...
“她有三个孩子：  Nat，Pat和Tat”
"she had three babies named nat, pat and tat...
“她说生孩子很有趣...”
"she said it was fun at the breeding...
“但是喂养它们却是另一回事儿”
"but found it was hell in the feeding...
“因为没有奶头（tit）给Tat了”  （双关语：tit for tat也指以牙还牙）
"when she saw there was no tit for tat."
你已经给我惹了不少麻烦
You have caused me no end of trouble.
现在该轮到我回报你了
But now i shall return the favor.
以牙还牙,对吧？
Tit for tat, right?
哦，对了 还有一件事儿
Now, see, that's the latest thing.
这枪只有确认主人的指纹后
The gun will only fire when it recognizes...
才能开火
the thumbprint of the owner.
这样既能避免走火  又降低了犯罪率
It makes firearms safer and it cuts down the crime too.
别让他跑了！
Get him!
你是谁？
Who are you?
夫人，你叫什么名字？
Lady, what's your name?
好枪法
Nice knockers.
∮我说过那个家伙很饥渴∮
## I said the joker is a wanted man ##
∮他想尽办法跨越那片土地∮
## he makes his way all across the land ##
∮他从沙漠中穿过∮
## see him sifting through the sand ##
该死的！
god damn it!
∮而我要告诉你整个的故事∮
## So i'll tell you all the story ##
∮关于那个家伙还有那晚的贼∮
## about the joker and the thief of the night ##
∮他总是嘲笑那些权贵∮
## he's always laughing in the midst of power ##
∮他总是能绝处逢生∮
## always living in the final hour ##
∮辛酸的生活中总有美好∮
## there is always sweet in the sour ##
操你妈的 你们这帮该死的混蛋
fuck you, ya fuckin' fuckers.
以牙还牙，大英雄 (后面的英文：Fuck u too，也操你妈）
Tit for tat, mr. Hero.
以牙还牙
Tit for tat.
把他抬进去，快点
Get him in there. Come on.
我来帮你抬，老板
I was goin' back for her, boss.
不用，我自己来
No, i got it.
嘿，我可不是那种只会站在一旁...
Hey, i'm not the head honcho who sits on his hands...
一边哈气，一边暖手...
warming them with his own exhaust...
而让手下们
while everybody else does the work.
拼命干活的人，对吧？
Every second counts, right?
这他妈的是怎么搞的？
Now, how the heck did this happen, huh?
本来一切都很顺利...
Everything was goin' smooth at the safe house...
...没想到那女的掏出一把枪
...when the woman draws a gun.
我的意思是…  谁会想到一个怀孕的女人会带着枪？
I mean, who expects a pregnant lady to pull a piece on ya, eh?
那么那个男的又是谁？  怎么会和她在一起？
And who was this man who was with her?
我不知道
I don't know.
那女的逃跑后  我们一直追着她到这里
After the woman escaped, we tracked her here.
那个家伙，本来是在...
This guy, he was hangin' around...
在公交车站乱逛的
at the bus stop.
我本来决定先解决那女的  再回来找他...
I mean, so we decided that we'd deal with him later...
但谁想到 当他看到我们追那女的…
but we go after the woman...
他也跟了过来
he gets in on the action. You know?
他拿出一把抢，然后朝我们开枪
He took a gun, he started shootin' at us,
这时候，你来了…
and that's... that's when y...
哦，好的，知道了
- oh. Ok. ...you arrived.
放松点，坐下
Take it easy. Sit down.
好的
All right.
哦！你还好吗？
Oh, you all right?
好吧
Ok.
你是不是想说…
Are you tryin' to tell me...
一个流浪汉来英雄救美？
that some bum came to her rescue?
哦，哦，哦  这可真是太糟糕了，是吧？
Well, well, well, this is a fine mess, huh?
我不会再犯同样的错误了
I won't make this mistake again.
我屁股里的弹片会一直提醒我的
Well, i got a piece of lead in my butt as a reminder.
好吧
Ok.
很高兴你这么想
I can appreciate that.
我的屁股！
My ass!
让它时刻提醒着你  别再让我失望
And let that be a reminder never to fail me again.
见鬼
Damn.
别让我为了个婴儿而杀了你
Don't make me kill you to get the baby.
退后
Back off.
亲爱的，任务快要完成了
Sweetie, this deal is almost done.
我已经订好了回去的机票
Look, i've already booked my flight home.
好吗？
Ok?
好的
Ok.
我也爱你
I love you too.
好，拜拜
Yeah. Bye-bye.
你们知道为什么枪要比老婆好吗？
You know why a gun is better than a wife?
不知道
Don't know.
因为你可以给枪装个消声器
Well, you can put a silencer on a gun.
先生，我们发现目标...
Sir, we spotted the target...
在第三大街和杰斐逊大街路口  正前往公园
at third and jefferson heading toward the park.
掉头
Turn us around.
来啊！爸爸！
Come on! Dad!
- 快来啊  - 好的
- Come on. - All right.
谁是爸爸的小宝贝呢？
Who's daddy's little girl?
别担心，孩子  会有好心人收留你的
Don't worry, kid. Someone good'll find you.
噢，我的天，快来看
Oh, my god, look at this.
有人忘了他的孩子
Someone left a baby.
歪了！
Oops.
真他妈的厉害！
Fuck me sideways.
欢迎回来，Smith先生
Welcome back, mr. Smith.
Quintana在哪儿？
Where's quintana?
等一下，Smith   Donna小姐有客人
Wait, smith, mistress donna's with a customer.
等一下，你不能就这么上去
Wait, you can't go up there.
哦耶，宝贝
Oh, yeah, baby.
- Smith？  - 这种感觉不错，是吧？
- Smith? - You like that, huh?
而且，我觉得Mary小姐更适合你
Besides, i thought mistress mary was more your type.
你不能上去
You can't go up there.
∮他是个坏男孩，这没关系∮
## I've got a bad boy and that's all right with me ##
∮他穿着肮脏，也没关系∮  来吧！
- ## his dirty laundry ## - come 'ere!
∮因为我也不干净∮
## Is nothing that i can't keep clean ##
∮而他需要释放自己∮
## and when he needs an alibi... ##
∮金钱∮
## money ##
∮金钱让这地球转动∮
## money makes the world go round ##
∮金钱∮
## money ##
∮金钱让你改变声调∮
## money make you change your sound ##
∮只要价格合适，只要价格合适∮
## if the price is right, if the price is right ##
抱歉，老兄 酒吧关门了
sorry, pal, the bar's closed.
∮如果你渴望黄金和白银∮
## If you want gold and silver ##
∮最终...∮
## sooner or later... ##
∮你不用认识你自己∮
## don't need to know yourself too well ##
还没轮到你呢，Smith
wait your turn, smith.
还有很多人在排队
There's plenty to go around.
我不排队，谢谢  我乳糖过敏
Not for me, thanks. I'm lactose intolerant.
那你告诉我你想要什么，Smith
Just tell me what you want, smith.
∮如果你寻求庇护∮
## If you want shelter ##
∮如果你想吸烟∮
## if you want smoke then you better ##
∮那么脱下你的毛衫∮
## take off your sweater ##
太奇怪了
kinky.
我想让你照顾这个孩子一段时间
I want you to take care of this baby for a while.
五千美金
Five grand.
应该能让你几个星期不用接客
That should keep you off your back for a couple of weeks.
你有污点记录吗？
Are you clean?
要知道，我可是一名优秀的“女童子军”  （世界青少年组织）
You know i'm a good girl scout.
这么说你答应了？
So you'll do it.
见你的鬼  你自己搞定，Smith
Vaffanculo. Screw yourself, smith.
我猜这个孩子肯定是你抢来的
For all i know, you snatched the kid.
我可不想成为绑架犯的帮凶
I don't want to be an accessory for kidnapping.
这孩子不是我偷来的  相信我
I didn't steal the kid, trust me.
相信你？
Trust you?
我甚至连你的真名都不知道
I don't even know your real name.
你到底是谁，Smith？
Who are you really, smith?
我是位英国保姆...
I'm a british nanny...
而且我是个危险人物
and i'm dangerous.
只需照顾这个孩子一天  你就能留下那捆钱
Just keep the baby for one day and you can keep the whole roll.
别做梦了，老兄
Forget it, dad.
好吧
Fine.
再见
Ciao.
奶水
Breast milk.
我们走
Let's go.
那个孩子肯定需要喝奶
This lady's baby needs to be fed.
把这个城市所有的奶妈  能喂奶的妓女…
Find me every wet nurse, lactating hooker...
以及所有能喂奶的女人  都给我找出来
and mammary on tap in the city.
我已经跟你说了，Smith
I already told you, smith, you're not welcome...
蜂蜜牛奶小屋不欢迎你
in the land of milk and honey.
我需要往咖啡里加点奶油  顺便打听点消息
I need a little cream for my coffee and some answers.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你们先回避一下
Scram, fellas.
让我和这位咖啡妈妈…
Give me a moment alone here with, uh...
单独谈谈
caffe la mamma.
放松，放松
Relax. Relax.
我的小蜜糖
Mia piccola troietta.
一个抱着婴儿的男人  曾经来过这里
There was a man here with a baby not too long ago.
对，一个十足的蠢蛋
Yes. A real jerk.
他想让我照顾那孩子
He wanted me to take care of the kid.
那么这男的叫什么名字？
And what is this man's name?
Smith
Smith.
Smith先生
Mr. Smith.
我怎么知道他的真名？
How the hell do i know his real name?
他来找过我几次…
He saw me a couple of times...
每次我都耍花招推诿他
when i was pulling straight tricks.
他也一直用Smith这个名字
He always used the same name... smith.
我不相信你
I don't believe you.
我想你知道的应该不止这些
I think you know more about this man.
他给小费很吝啬
He was a lousy tipper.
开枪次数越多枪管越热
It gets hotter the more times it's fired.
如果我知道的话  我一定会告诉你的
If i had anything on him, i'd tell you.
我放得越近就会越痛
And it gets a lot more painful the closer i get.
你好，老兄！
What's up, doc?
哦，你以为自己是只“长耳兔”  （卡通形象，聪明顽皮）
Oh, you're a "wascally wabbit."
可惜你的耳朵还不够“长”
But you're not "wascally" enough.
是吗？
Yeah?
你的枪是六发装
That's a six-shooter.
我听到你已经开完了六枪
I just counted six shots.
你现在已经没子弹了
You've blown your load.
那你的呢？
Yeah, well, what about you?
你那把9毫米手枪还不是一样也空了
Your 9-millimeter is empty too.
你在屋顶上开了八枪  在厕所开了一枪...
Yeah, you fired 8 on the rooftop, one in the men's room...
而且你的备用弹夹在广场上时  就已经用完
and your second cartridge was expended at the playground.
要是你抢了我手下的枪  那也发射不了
And you won't be getting it up with that gun you took off my man.
你知道的，像我们用的这种枪…
Oh, no. Well, you see, like my weapon...
都有指纹识别装置
it also has the thumbprint safety device.
哦，是吗？
Oh, really?
要赌一把吗？
Wanna bet?
这手还真不错  （语意双关：没有什么比手淫更好了）
Nothin' like a good hand job.
收拾行李，我们离开这里
Get your things. We're goin'.
虽然我不懂你说的是什么...
I don't understand a word you're going on about...
但是我知道你的意思 我拒绝道歉
but i know exactly what you're saying and i refuse to apologize.
你去死吧，Smith  我刚才差点就玩完了
Damn you, smith. I could have been snuffed back there.
是啊，你该感谢我  保住了你漂亮的后门
Yeah, you should be thanking me for saving your sweet back door.
你为什么等那么久才进来？
Why did you wait so goddamn long?
你是个坏女人  坏女人应该被惩罚一下
You're a bad girl, you deserve to be punished.
你想要哪辆车？
Which car do you want?
- 什么意思？  - 我走累了
- What? - I'm tired of walking.
瞧那边  （残障人士专用停车位）
Look at this.
你想知道…
You wanna know the difference...
这辆豪华轿车和豪猪  有什么不同吗？
between this luxury car and a porcupine?
不知道
I give up.
对于车来说  “刺”是隐藏在里面的
With the car, the pricks are on the inside.
你真有材
Tell me about it.
嗨，宝贝
Hello, honey.
噢，好，好，很高兴...
Oh, good, good, i'm glad...
很高兴你喜欢那些花
i'm glad you liked the flowers. Good.
听着，宝贝...
Listen, sweetie...
我这边遇到了点小麻烦
i've run into a small hitch.
恐怕我得多耽搁些时间
I think i'm gonna have to be out here for a while longer.
不过别担心
But don't worry.
Timmy的生日聚会  我肯定会到场的...
I will be back in time for timmy's birthday party...
我发誓
i swear to you.
拥抱亲吻你
Hugs and kisses.
拜拜
Bye-bye.
那我该怎么办？
So, what was i supposed to do?
那些人在追那个孕妇
These guys were stalking this pregnant lady.
我不能袖手旁观
I couldn't just stand there.
你看到没有  我他妈就讨厌这种人
Did you see that? I fuckin' hate that.
- 怎么了？  - 这种人随便变道
- What? - This guy, changin' lanes...
也不打转向灯
without signaling.
我的意思是  打个转向灯能有多难？
I mean, how hard is it to use your signal?
然后你开始朝他们开枪？
So you started shooting at them?
不是，我身上没有枪
No, i don't carry a piece.
我朝那个女人走去  她有枪
I went to the woman. She had a gun.
他们开枪，我还击
They started firing, i shot back.
他又来了
He's done it again.
我只需移动手指一寸...
I move my finger one inch...
就能按转向灯
to use my turn signal.
为什么这帮混蛋这么懒…
Why are these assholes so lazy...
只需他妈的移动手指一寸  就能驾驶得更安全
they can't move their finger one fucking measly inch...
他们都懒得动？
to drive more safely?
- 想知道为什么吗？  - 不是特别想
- You wanna know why? - Not particularly.
因为这帮纨绔子弟  为了赚钱…
Because these rich bastards have to...
已经变得冷漠无情  丝毫不顾及他人了
be callous and inconsiderate in the first place...
所以他们开车时…
to make all that money, so when they get on the road...
也很难控制自己…
they can't help themselves. They've gotta be...
丝毫不顾及他人
callous and inconsiderate drivers too.
这是他们的本性
It's in their nature.
你为什么不把这孩子交给警察？
Why don't you take the baby to the police?
- 我不能去警察局  - 为什么不能？
- I can't go to the police. - Why not?
我就是那个“炸弹人”
I'm the unabomber.
他们已经抓到他了
They caught the unabomber.
他们也希望这样
That's what they think.
这个蠢蛋…
Stupid...
好吧，给你点颜色看看
right. That's it.
你是世界上最暴躁的人
You are the angriest man in the world.
如果我没记错的话  你过去非常喜欢这种感觉
If i remember right, you used to like it like that.
你一共找了多少人？
Well, how many freelancers have you got?
就这些？有多少本地人？
Yeah? How many local boys?
我需要人手，明白吗？
I need men, you understand?
我需要更多的人
I need a lot more men.
∮听我唱歌∮
## Listen to my song ##
我要四个弹夹
i want four mags...
一盒9毫米147型中空子弹...
a box of 9-millimeter 147 hollow-points...
...还有50发全披甲弹
...and give me 50 fmjs.
你的钱不够
You're a little short.
你骗人，你说你有5000美元的
You lied. You said you had $5,000.
不够的用粮食券替代怎么样？
How about we make up the difference with food stamps?
你想用粮食券买子弹？
You wanna buy bullets with food stamps?
这个跟现金没什么区别
It's as good as cash.
你真可怜，Smith
You're pathetic, smith.
我们在外面等你
We'll wait for you outside.
这张从献血站得来的支票怎么样？
Look, why don't i sign over this check i got at the blood bank to you?
已经有余了
Lt'll more than cover it.
如果再加上那张你从  精子捐献中心得到的支票...
Throw in that check you got from the sperm bank...
就差不多了
and got yourself a deal.
周三前我是拿不到那张支票的
I don't get that check till wednesday.
这样吧  你可以先拿走半盒子弹
Listen, why don't you take a half-a box of shells...
如果你在周三能把钱补齐的话
and i'll give you the other half...
我会给你剩下的半盒
when you bring me the rest of the money on wednesday.
成交
Deal.
见鬼，Smith！
Damn it, smith!
你这是他妈的干什么？
What the hell are you doing?
赚点外快
Making some money.
- 赚点外快？  - 对
- Making some money? - Well, yeah.
得给孩子买点东西
To buy something for the baby.
给孩子买东西？
Something for the baby?
防弹背心看起来  比婴儿床更值得投资
A bulletproof vest is a better investment than a crib.
让我想到了你会怎么做  才能让他上个好学校
Makes me think what you'd do to get him in the right school.
就是这儿了
So this is it.
虽然不是很华丽  但至少能算个家
It's not the ritz but it's home.
看上去都那么的古老
Same old smith.
破旧不堪
Down and dirty.
很高兴你喜欢这儿
Glad you like it.
跟米奇打个招呼
Say hello to mickey.
也许我该把孩子交给警察
Maybe i should take the baby to the police.
不行，你办不到
No, you'd never make it.
他们会在整个辖区  布下天罗地网
They'll be watching all the precincts...
同时收买些穿蓝制服的手下
probably got some of the boys in blue on payola too.
我已经叫来了50个人
I've rounded up 50 guys.
这也是逼不得已的选择，是吧？
Well, i guess that's just gonna have to do, huh?
停车，他在那边
Stop the car. He was here.
别逗了，你怎么知道他在那边？
Come on, what makes you think he was here?
相信我  我知道人们脑子里都在想什么
Trust me. I know what people do and i know what people think.
自从小时候就一向如此  这是天赋
I always have. Even as a kid, i had this gift.
你要是跟过我玩过石头剪子布
Yeah, you shoulda seen the playground hurt i laid down...
就知道有多么痛苦了，老兄
playin' rock, paper, scissors, buddy.
现在给我停车
Now stop the car.
到底谁要杀这个孩子？
Who do you think wants this baby dead?
我也不清楚谁要杀它
I've no idea who's tryin' to kill it.
别用“它”这个字
Don't call him an "it."
在我看来就是“它”
It's an "it" to me.
告诉我，Smith  这个世界上有你喜欢的东西吗？
Tell me, smith, is there anything you like?
有，我的隐私
Yeah, my privacy.
除了这个你还会说什么
Tell me something i don't know per una volta...
你这个狗娘养的混蛋
brutto figlio di puttana bastardo.
我喜欢你这样说话的口气
I love it when you talk like that.
想吃点什么？
Can i offer you anything?
胡萝卜？
Carrot?
对视力有好处
It's good for your eyesight.
这个城市这么多废弃的房子...
Of all the squats in the city...
他怎么确定就是这座楼？
how does he know smith's in this one?
又是幸运的猜测？
Another lucky guess?
他可不是靠猜的
Nah, he doesn't guess.
他能看到我们看不到的东西
He sees things we don't.
他曾经是联邦调查局的  行为分析专家
He was once an fbi profiler.
法医行为顾问
Forensic behavior consultant.
天呐，我得说多少次  你们才会记住？
My god, how many times do i have to tell you guys?
细节…
Details...
...在这个领域里决定一切
...make all the difference in this business.
嘿，但是…
Hey, but...
你不认为你最好走在后面吗，先生？
don't... you think you should hang back, sir?
躲在后面的领导只能吃残羹冷滞
The leader who stays in the rear, takes it in the rear.
而且
Besides...
暴力是这个世界上  最有趣，值得一看的东西
violence is one of the most fun things to watch.
别哭了，宝贝 别哭了
No, no, no, baby, no.
我们可以叫他“Oliver”
We could call him oliver.
- Oliver？  - 就像OliverTwist  （狄更斯小说《雾都孤儿》的主人公）
- Oliver? - Yeah, like oliver twist.
因为他是个孤儿？
Because he's an orphan?
因为我喜欢那本书
'Cause i like the book.
- 你喜欢那本书？  - 我不讨厌那书
- You like the book. - I didn't hate it.
这是第一次你用“喜欢”这个词
That's a first.
你们觉得我应该选哪张生日卡片？
Which birthday card do you think i should go with here?
让人想拥抱的可爱卡通？
Cute and cuddly?
或是这个写的：  “你正成长为男人，儿子”
Or the one that says, "you're becomin' a man now, son"?
Hertz先生，请问
So, mr. Hertz?
你儿子几岁了？
How old is your son?
今年8岁
He's 8.
（这已经演变成一场重量级的...）
Then it had to be large and powerful and...
真不敢相信？
can you believe it?
电视上...
There's nothing on the tv...
根本没有报道此事
- about any of this. ...without a trace.
（...路旁炸弹爆炸事件造成...）
...roadside bomb wounded...
（我们相信…）
we have it in our...
嘿，你注意到没有？
hey. Do you notice that?
注意什么？
Notice what?
你看
Look.
听喋喋不休的政客畅谈枪支管制  他会一直哭
Lame-ass politician rants about gun control, he cries.
- （今晚...）  - 如果我转到这个...
- So tonight... - switch to this channel...
重金属音乐...
with this heavy metal music...
...他就不哭了
...he shuts up.
太奇怪了
That's so weird.
他肯定很喜欢这音乐
He must find it comforting.
- 先生？  - 什么事？
- Sir? - Yeah?
- 屋顶上的人已经就绪  - 很好
- Men are in place on the roof. - That's good.
有人知道Jimmy Cagney 演的爱情戏结局是什么吗？  （Jimmy Cagney，第15届奥斯卡影帝）
Anybody know what a jimmy cagney love scene is?
就是他总放过那些好人
It's where cagney lets the good guy live.
如果这出戏也是这样…
And if that happens in this show...
我可不会只把钱要回来
i'm gonna do a lot more than ask for my money back.
明白没？ 干掉这个母亲，走！
All right? Let's kill this mother. Go.
Oliver喜欢重金属音乐  我觉得一点也不稀奇
It doesn't surprise me that oliver's into death metal.
看看他现在的父母
Look at his surrogate parents.
不，我告诉你  这意味着…
No, i'm telling ya, this means...
快走，从后门
go. Back way.
∮如果你喜欢赌博∮
## If you like to gamble ##
∮我告诉你，我们是同一种人∮
## i tell you i'm your man ##
∮你时赢时输，我也一样∮
## you win some, lose some, it's still the same to me ##
∮玩到尽情∮
## playing for the high one ##
∮与魔鬼共舞∮
## dancing with the devil ##
∮跟着感觉走∮
## going with the flow ##
∮对我来说，这一切都只是一场游戏∮
## it's all a game to me ##
∮7还是11∮
## seven or eleven ##
∮蛇的双眼正盯着你∮
## snake eyes watching you ##
∮加码还是退出∮
## double up or quit ##
∮加大赌金还是转身离开∮
## double stake or split ##
∮\桃A，\桃A∮
## the ace of spades, the ace of spades ##
∮你知道我是天生的失败者∮
## you know i'm born to lose ##
∮赌博是给傻瓜的娱乐∮
## and gambling's for fools ##
∮但我就喜欢它这点，宝贝∮
## but that's the way i like it, baby ##
∮我不求永生∮
## i don't wanna live forever ##
∮不要忘记了还有王∮
## and don't forget the joker ##
∮加大赌注∮
## pushing up the ante ##
∮我知道你已经看到我∮
## i know you've got to see me ##
∮看着我的牌落泪∮
## read 'em and weep ##
∮又是一手烂牌∮
## the dead man's hand again ##
∮我从你的眼中看到了这一切∮
## i see it in your eyes ##
∮只需看一眼，然后死去∮
## take one look and die ##
∮你所看到的∮
## the only thing you see ##
∮你知道会是∮
## you know it's gonna be ##
∮那张\桃A∮
## the ace of spades ##
我的上帝！  是我们真的太逊...
my god, do we really suck...
还是这家伙真的很强？
or is this guy really that good?
快给我追！
Come on, boys!
他还在我的掌心之中！
He ain't out of the briar patch yet!
射死那条狗，快射死那条狗
Shoot the dog, shoot the dog.
不
No.
- 为什么不？  - 我喜欢狗
- Why not? - I like dogs.
等一下
Wait a minute.
是只该死的老鼠
Oh, that rat bastard.
那是什么？
What is it?
婴儿尿布
It's the baby's diaper.
你的想法太荒谬了，Smith
This idea blows, smith.
我们只能这么办了
It's the only idea we got.
你真的认为Oliver的妈妈
You actually think that oliver's mother...
住在重金属俱乐部的附近
lived near a heavy metal club...
所以他还在子宫里时  就在听那种音乐？
...and that he could hear the music while he was still inside the womb?
对，这也是他为什么
Yep. That's why he doesn't cry...
听到金属打击声不哭
when he's listenin' to some headbanger's bash.
真荒谬
Ridiculous.
瞧，他现在不是没哭吗！
Well, he isn't cryin' now.
我遇到他妈妈的地方附近  只有这家俱乐部
So this is the only club near where i encountered the baby's mother.
我坚持这只是你疯狂的预感
I still say this is a wild hunch.
是吗？那你怎么解释这么多尿布盒子？
Yeah? So how do you explain all these boxes of diapers?
一定是有人买了很多来备用
Somebody's been stocking up.
让我们看看到底是谁
Let's find out who.
∮你燃烧我的大腿  像鸟叫一样愉快∮
## You sear my legs, song birds cheer ##
∮啃我的脖子∮
## eat my neck ##
∮我不能  我不能让气氛下去∮
## i can't, i can't let it go grey ##
∮我挣脱不开，我挣脱不开∮
## i can't break, i can't break ##
∮我挣脱不开，我挣脱不开 我挣脱不开∮
## i can't break, i can't break, i can't break ##
- 你是这儿的老板？  - 谁叫我？
- you the owner of this place? - Who's askin'?
我叫的
I am.
- 能请你喝一杯吗？  - 免了
- Can i buy you a drink? - No.
不出我所料
Just as i suspected.
它真的穿了环
He really is into jewelry.
谁住在楼上？
Who occupies the room upstairs?
去死吧
Go to hell.
别惹怒我
Don't mess with me.
你扯不下那环的
You ain't got the cojones.
噢，上帝
Oh, god.
这些都是什么人？
So who were these guys?
11个月前我把这地方租给了  一个西装革履的家伙
I rented the place to some suit 11 months ago.
他用现金付了一年的租金
He paid the whole year in cash.
但后来就一直没再见过他
I never saw him again.
我猜他们可能只走后门
I just figured they were usin' the back way.
你可以走了
Beat it.
哦，我的天
Oh, madonna.
太恐怖了！
Che orrore!
真是一团糟
This is pretty fucked up.
先生，我是执行者
Sir, it's your go-to guy.
所有的孕妇都被杀了
All the mothers have been killed.
只有一个跑掉，暂时的
Only one escaped, temporarily.
因为我们找到了她的尸体  并且确认她已经生了个孩子
We found her body and confirmed that she did deliver a child.
孩子本应该秘密的生产
The babies were supposed to be delivered covertly.
但我认为把产房建在  重金属俱乐部的上面
I guess setting up this maternity factory...
并不是很隐蔽
on top of a heavy metal club wasn't particularly secret.
所以我们需要更多的“保姆”
What a fine lot of babysitters we turned out to be.
当执行者过去后，往左边走
When mr. Go-to guy passes, head to the left.
是的，先生  我已经汇报了
Yes, sir, i already made the call.
增援马上就到
Backup should be arriving any minute.
我们要清理现场  还要把这里发生的细节
We'll clean this mess up and try to piece together...
尽量拼凑起来
everything that happened.
谢谢，先生  感谢您对我的信任
Thank you, sir. I appreciate your confidence.
先生们，让我们找到答案
Gentlemen, let's find some answers.
注意脚下
Watch where you step.
- 冰淇淋正在融化  - 什么？
- The ice cream is melting. - What?
我还以为捐献精子是在你们部门呢！  （影射她是妓女）
I thought donor sperm was your department.
冷藏柜里全是精子样品
These freezers are full of samples.
奇怪了
This is weird.
似乎只有一个人在捐献
There seems to be only one donor.
一个人？
One donor?
是的，他对此可真是慷慨
Yeah. And a generous one at that.
这是骨髓血
This is bone marrow blood.
一定是用来治某种病的
It must be for some kind of cure.
你怎么知道，Smith？
How do you know that, smith?
你没听说我得过诺贝尔奖吗？
You didn't hear about my nobel prize?
很难找到与受捐者一致的骨髓
See, what it is, it's hard to find marrow that matches that of the recipient.
但如果捐献者与受捐者
The odds are much better if the donor marrow shares...
有相同的DNA  那一致的机率就会大很多
the same dna with the person receiving it.
你是说这些人培育婴儿
You mean these people were harvesting babies...
是为了给某人做骨髓移植？
for some guy's bone marrow transplant?
没错，但还有某些人  不想让他得到骨髓
Exactly. And somebody wanted to make sure he didn't get it.
所以他们要杀掉Oliver
That's why they want oliver dead.
不哭，宝贝，不哭
No, my baby, no.
我已经给国家广播电台（NBC）  的熟人打了电话
So i called that guy i know at nbc.
很好
That's good.
然后我又想
And then i got to thinking.
- 你知道我讨厌什么吗？ - 又来了
- You know what i hate? - Here we go again.
我讨厌那些蹩脚的动作片里
I hate those lame action movies...
好人只给一个人打电话  而他因为被出卖以死告终
where the good guy calls just one person who ends up betrayin' him.
是呀，他们会来杀这孩子的
Yeah. That's right up there with killing baby seals.
所以我打电话给美国广播公司  哥伦比亚比亚广播公司、邮报、泰晤士报
I called abc, cbs, the post, the times...
地方新闻频道，还有联邦调查局
the local news channel, and the fbi.
那我们下一步怎么办？
So, what do we do next?
暂时待在这儿看新闻
I figure we hang here and watch the news.
如果事情暴光  我们或许就安全了
Once the story goes public, maybe we'll be safe.
看，他终于睡着了
Look. He finally went to sleep.
你等着看
Yeah, you just wait.
只要你一闭眼休息  他就又会大哭大叫了
The moment you close your eyes for a nap, he'll start screaming.
你对什么事情都没有兴趣，对吧？
You can't take a little pleasure in anything, can you?
你讨厌所有的事情
You just hate everything.
我不讨厌你
I don't hate you.
这就是为什么你选中了我？
Is that why you picked me?
你知道我为什么选你
You know why i picked you.
但你不知道  你对我做了什么
You have no idea what you've done to me.
相信我，我们会脱身的
We're gonna get out of this, trust me.
- 你根本就不明白  - 什么？
- You just don't get it. - What?
你把这个婴儿交给我  让我喂养他，照顾他
You bring me this child so i can feed him, take care of him.
但他随时都有可能被杀死
A baby that could be dead at any moment.
而你从来没有问过我
And you never even think to ask me...
我自己的孩子怎么了？
what happened to my own child.
你说得对
You're right.
这是不可原谅的
It's unforgivable.
不，是我的错
No. It's my fault.
就像我妈妈常说的
It's like what my mamma always said...
“le uova non devono  ballare con le pietre.”
"le uova non devono ballare con le pietre."
如果我向你道歉  你能告诉我那是什么意思吗？
If i say i'm sorry will you tell me what that means?
永远不要拿鸡蛋碰石头
Eggs have no business dancing with stones.
你知道吗，Smith
You know, smith...
我终于知道你最讨厌什么了
i figured out what you hate most...
你自己
yourself.
你的孩子怎么了？
What happened to your baby?
忘了吧！
Forget about it.
告诉我
Tell me.
我的嫖客撞我的肚子
My pimp hit me in the stomach.
我的孩子...
My baby...
流产夭折了
was delivered stillborn.
- 放开我  - 嘿
- Get off of me! - Hey.
你喜欢这个，是吗？
You like this, do ya?
这叫枪
It's called a gun.
枪托、套筒、后膛、枪管、板机
Grip, slide, breech, barrel, trigger.
这是枪口
Now, this is the business end.
永远不要把枪口指向  任何你不想杀死的东西
You should never point this at anything you don't intend to kill.
这个很重要，这是保险
Now, this is important. This is called your safety.
你要一直开着它  以确保枪不会走火
You have to keep this on to make sure the gun doesn't go off accidentally.
但实际上，这个才是你的一号保险
But really, this is your number one safety.
你饿吗？
Are you hungry?
∮我看着这些年轻迷离的双眼∮
## I watched those youthful paisley eyes ##
∮他们像孩子一样盯着荧幕∮
## they drink the screen just like a child ##
下面的“枪”法怎样？
talk about shootin' your load.
看看这个
Look at this.
这是Hammerson公司的Nite tac型手枪
This is a hammerson nite tac.
它们应该在六个月后才上市
These aren't supposed to hit the streets for 6 months.
有点奇怪
This is weird.
这些人都用这种枪
All these guys have got 'em.
不用说了
Don't even tell me.
你知道他杀了我们多少人吗？
Do you know how many of our men he's body-bagged now?
我为什么要  浪费我的聪明才智去想这种事？
Why should i waste my beautiful mind on something like that?
你一点也不生气？
Doesn't it piss you off a little?
生气会让你产生一种酶
Getting angry releases an enzyme...
色氨酸羟化酶
tryptophan hydroxylase...
它会让智商暂时性降低
which can temporarily reduce the i.q.
这可是我现在负担不起的
That's something i can't afford to do right now.
你怎么会懂这些？
How do you know all that?
我儿子整天看探索频道
My boy's hooked on the discovery channel.
带我回总部，我得向上面汇报
Take me westside. I need to report in.
我们的英雄有线索了
I got a bead on who our mr. Hero is.
不要再争了
No more arguments.
我必须一个人去  只有确保你们俩的安全后
I have to do this alone, and the only way i can do it...
我才能大胆去干
is if i'm positive you two are ok.
这是唯一我认为安全的地方
This is the only place i know you'll be safe.
- 坦克？  - 一辆M24型坦克
- A tank? - An m24 tank.
在里面你能躲避子弹  和绝大多数的爆炸
You'll be safe from gunfire and most explosives.
- 你疯了  - 没错
- You're whacked. - I am.
我是说真的
I'm also serious.
但任何人都不被允许进去
But nobody's allowed to get in it.
别担心，我吸引他们的注意力  你趁机爬进去
Don't worry. When i create a diversion, you climb inside.
你应该有足够
You should have enough of that baby food...
让婴儿喝几天的奶吧！
to last you a couple of days.
生吃胡萝卜是最好的
The pureed carrots are the best.
你知道怎么用这个，对吧？
Well, you know how to use this, right?
是的，但如果你回不来怎么办？
Yes, but what if you don't come back?
那不可能
That's not gonna happen.
你没办法百分之百保证
There is no way to be sure.
我能保证
Yes, there is.
你是英雄，是我的英雄
Tu sei una stella, la mia stella.
- 妈妈，我要回家  - 别闹了
- But, mom, i wanna go home! - Stop whining!
你要是再不老实  我就打你屁股
If you don't behave, i am going to spank you.
- 妈妈，我要回家  - 别闹了
- But, mom, i wanna go home! - Stop whining.
不要再闹了
Stop it!
我最讨厌父母…
I hate it when parents...
- 打他们的孩子  - 放开我的胳膊！
- hit their children. - Let go of my arm!
除非你不再打他
Not until you stop hittin' your kid.
怎么管教小孩是我自己的事
I will discipline my child as i see fit.
那你喜不喜欢我打你屁股？
How would you like it if i spanked you?
什么？
What?
- 怎样？  - 救命！
- See? - Help!
感觉不好，是吧？
Doesn't feel so good, does it?
救命！
Help!
你他妈的这是在干什吗？
What the hell do you think you're doin'?
这不好笑！
It's not funny.
有查到关于那个硬汉的什么吗？
So, what you got on this all-star ground pounder?
那么厉害的人  通常是自小就很出色
Well, anybody this good had to start out young.
通常也是因为他们的父亲  非常厉害
And it's usually because their pop was good at it too.
就像Macarthur（麦克阿瑟：美五星上将）  的父亲是个将军...
You know, like macarthur's dad was a general...
Mickey Mantle（美职业棒球员） 的父亲是职业棒球手
and mickey mantle's father played pro ball.
我儿子是个电子游戏高手...
My son is a video game whiz...
而我玩得也不差
and i wasn't too bad at pong myself.
请继续听我说  如果你愿意，Hammerson先生
Just follow me, if you will, mr. Hammerson.
1967年，英国实施严厉的枪支管制
In '67, the limeys got hard-ass on gun control.
所以很多造枪的英国人  来到美国
So a lot of brit gunsmiths moved to the states.
我在移民局的一个线人...
Now, i've got an inside man at lmmigration...
正在查这些人中...
working on which of these guys had sons...
谁的儿子是个神枪手
and if any of the boys were crack shots.
你想的这都是什么狗屁东西
I think the pucker factor's gettin' to you.
你真能扯淡！
You got diddly!
好的，公爵夫人  好女孩，坐下
Yes, duchess, you a good girl. Sit.
现在是你享受的时刻了
Yes. Now's your treat. Now you get your treat.
我的人逐个追查这些人...
My man has been running the name down...
并发现其中一个造枪人的儿子
and he recalled one of these gunsmith kids, actually.
十岁时获得全国运动会射击冠军...
National sports pistol champion at age 10...
有望参加奥运会  却被征招入伍
olympic hopeful, recruited by the army.
- 但从那以后，这个孩子...  - 亲亲，亲亲
- But after that, the kid is... - kisses, kisses, kisses.
...就消失了
...never heard from again.
看起来像是秘密特工组织  找到他，并培训他
Well, that sounds like black ops got him, trained him.
- 于是我总结出一个理论  - 理论？
- This leads me to a theory. - A theory?
理论就是狗屁
A theory is bull-noogies.
你找到的只是一个无名小卒
All you got is a man with no name...
骑着一匹瘦马冲进城堡
ridin' into town on a pale horse...
宣扬自己标榜的正义
dispensin' his own brand o' justice.
Hertz，你知道这个国家的人  为什么这么喜欢枪吗？
Hertz, you know why people in this country love guns?
这和生殖器崇拜
And it's got nothin' to do with all that...
比如“武装阳具”的没什么关系
phallic mumbo jumbo, like "cockin' your gun."
Hertz，人们喜欢枪...
No, hertz, people love guns...
因为美国是机遇的天堂
because america is a land of opportunity...
这里穷人能够变得富有...
where a poor man can become rich...
胆小鬼也能变成硬汉
...and a pussy can become a tough guy...
只要他手里有把枪
if he's got a gun in his hand.
我希望你不是  手里拿着枪的胆小鬼
I'm hopin' you're not just a pussy with a gun in your hand.
哦，不不，先生  我不是
Oh, no, sir, no. No, i'm not.
我是一个手握胆小鬼的硬汉
I'm a tough guy with a pussy in my hand.
我要你杀了这个家伙
I want you to give this guy...
还有那个婴儿
and the kid a dirt nap.
好的，先生
Yes, sir.
机会来了，先生
Right away, sir.
我的小宝贝
Amore mio.
别担心
Don't worry.
爸爸一会儿就会回来
Daddy will be back soon.
停一下，停一下
Hold it! Hold it!
哦，哦，兔子先生
Well, well, well, mr. Bunny.
你还在不断地蹦来蹦去，是吧？
You just keep goin', goin', goin', don't ya?
- 你也是  - 我保证...
- So do you. - I promise to, uh...
保证不杀你，只要你告诉我...
to spare your life if you tell me where...
那个女人和婴儿在哪儿
the woman and child are.
做梦吧
Forget it.
哦，伙计
Oh, boy.
谁训练你的
'Ey, who trained you?
国家安全局的秘密特工组织？  中央情报局？还是军队？
N.s.a. Black ops? Cia? The army?
不管是谁，你枪法很准，冠军
Well, whoever. It seems you haven't lost your aim, champ.
这就很好吗？  你还没看到我在雪地里射出我的名字！
You think that's good, you should see me spell my name in the snow.
我的老板也在这里
'Ey, you know, my boss here...
他认为你是个孤独战士或什么的
thinks that you're the lone ranger or something.
不过，我觉得我更了解你
Well, i believe i have a better idea about who you are.
我查到你的老婆和儿子  是怎么死的
I found out how your wife and son were killed.
哦，天呐！ 太悲惨了
My god, what a tragedy.
有人走进汉堡店
Some guy walks into a burger joint...
然后开始开枪扫射
he starts shooting up the place.
哦，天呀！ 太遗憾了
Oh, my god, what a shame...
当时你的老婆和儿子
that your wife and son were there...
正在那儿吃鸡块
having their... chicken nuggets.
怎么了，你不喜欢这个故事？
What's the matter, ya don't like that story?
好，那你给我讲一个吧
Well, then why don't ya tell me one, hm?
来个少儿故事
Children's story, please.
说一个你感兴趣的故事吧
告诉我关于那个婴儿的故事
Tell me the one about the baby.
或许等一会...
Maybe later...
等我让你们都睡下再讲
when i put you to sleep.
上，上!
Go, go!
你觉得我这进一步的改进如何？
So, what do you think of this second amendment now?
操你妈！
Fuck you!
好了，伙计 把枪放下
Ok, buddy, drop your weapon.
抓住他了？
Think we got him?
真他妈见鬼，Smith！
God damn it, smith!
我查出了是谁想杀死这个婴儿
So i found out who's tryin' to kill our baby.
- 谁？  - 一个叫Hammerson的家伙
- Who? - A man named hammerson.
出生时屁股就夹一把金勺子  （讽：出生于有钱人家）
Born with a silver spoon up his ass.
从他老爸那里继承了Hammer武器公司...
Inherited the hammer firearms corporation...
靠制造武器发了大财
from his old man and makes millions manufacturing weapons.
那这些能让你想到是谁
Does this give you any new ideas...
想要Oliver的骨髓吗？
about who needs oliver's bone marrow?
还不能
No.
没关系，小Oliver
It's ok, little oliver.
狗屎！是他
Shit. It's him.
Rutledge议员
Senator rutledge.
如果他当选总统  他会让Hammerson公司停业破产
If he's elected president, he'll put hammerson out of business.
有道理，但你怎么这么确定？
It makes sense, but how can you be sure?
那个执行者打电话时说  需要更多的“保姆”
Mr. Go-to guy called his men a fine lot of babysitters.
情报局也让他们的特工  去保护那些“保姆”
The secret service calls their agents who guard vips babysitters.
就是他，Rutledge议员
It's him, senator rutledge.
就是他需要这个婴儿
He's the guy that needs this baby.
那我们联系上他  我们就安全了
So we contact this man and then we're safe.
- 就结束了  - 你疯了吗？
- It's over. - Are you crazy?
这样的话不仅是Hammerson...
This means that we've got hammerson...
还有整个美国政府都会来追杀我们
and the whole of the u.s. Government after us.
你们俩得离开这里
I think you two have gotta get out of town.
直到我解决完这件事  你们俩才能安全
Until i get the answers, you'll never be safe.
他们会监视火车站  汽车站和飞机场
They'll be watchin' the trains, the bus stations and the airports...
所以这是你们离开的最安全办法
so i think this is the safest way to get out of town.
我要去把这件事做个了结  如果一切顺利
I'm gonna check all of this out, and if everything's ok...
我会在你们上车离开前和你们碰面
i'll get you before you board the bus.
但是…如果在我们走之前  你没来怎么办？
But... what if you don't get to us before we leave?
那我应该在哪里下车？
Where should i get off?
我想我不知道为好
I think it's better if i don't know.
- 什么？  - 相信我
- What? - Trust me.
我不能知道
I can't know.
Smith，你认为这样真的能行吗？
Smith, do you really think this is gonna work?
如果一切按计划行事  应该没有问题
Just stick to the plan and everything will be all right.
快跑！
Run!
你们的安全带系得太紧了
So much for wearin' your seat belt.
那是什么鬼东西？
What in the hell is that?
哦，天哪! 是个陷阱
Oh, my god, that is twisted.
那个婊子养的混蛋
That sick son of a bitch.
哦，那个婊子养的混蛋  又把我们给耍了
Oh, that sick son of a bitch suckered us again!
小宝贝，我们该走了
It's time to go, little boy.
帮我接通任何一个  Rutledge议员的保镖
Put me through to whoever's protecting senator rutledge.
告诉他是个带着婴儿的人打来的
Just tell him there's a man with a baby calling.
你好，是Smith吗？
Hello, is this smith?
你们在市区培育婴儿的事情  掩盖的不错
That was a nice job coverin' up your baby hatchery downtown.
新闻里一点没提
Not a word about it anywhere.
只有你们这些在华盛顿的人  才有这种能耐
Only you guys in washington have that kind of pull.
我想告诉你，我们是一条船上的
I'm telling you, we're on the same side.
听着，这件事可以很简单  也可以很复杂
Now, listen, we can do this the easy way or the hard way.
我想见议员
I wanna see the senator.
好的，他也想见你
All right. He wants to see you too.
他正要去North Carolina州  初选将在三天后进行
He's leaving for north carolina. The primary's in three days.
你可以和他乘同一架飞机  七号跑道，两个小时后起飞
You can fly with him. Runway 7, two hours.
如果你们搞花样  我就把事情闹大
I see anythin' i don't like, i'm blowin' this big time.
你在里面做什么？
What were you doing in there?
- 擦枪  - 真的？
- Cleaning my gun. - Really?
你知道，我们从来  没想过要真的杀你
You know, we were never really trying to kill you.
我们只是想逼你投降而已
We only wanted to scare you into surrendering.
这倒可以解释  为什么你们总打不中我
Well, that's one way to explain why you can't shoot straight.
最新的民意调查显示，Rutledge议员
In the latest poll, senator rutledge...
继续领先于其它民主党候选人
continues to be the democratic frontrunner...
到下周二的大选
heading into next week's super tuesday primary.
他会领先对手至少十个百分点
He leads his rival by at least 10 points...
我欠你一条命
i owe you my life.
这就是你处理那些妓女的地方？
So this is where you get to do all those hookers.
- 我听说过你  - 你看起来没有电视里精神
- I heard about you. - You look worse than you do on tv.
是的，很神奇吧  化妆的效果不同凡想
Yes, it's amazing what a little makeup can do.
还有大量的吗啡
And a lot of morphine.
你已经把所有细节都拼凑起来了
So, you've pieced the whole thing together.
非常聪明，Smith先生  非常聪明
Very clever, mr. Smith. Very clever.
很简单
Simple.
你是民主党的头号候选人
You're the democratic frontrunner for president...
你的对枪支管制的提议
and your sweeping gun control proposals...
惹恼了不该惹的人
are pissing the wrong people off.
如果他们现在已经生气  等我当上总统他们就更有得瞧了
Yes, well, if they're pissed now, wait until i'm elected president.
我们有太多该死的
We got so many goddamn...
枪械店
gun lobbies out there...
所以我们要提出很多议案
that we're gonna have to set up just as many commissions.
或许我们的议案第一年就能通过
Then maybe we'll get our bill passed in the first year.
不幸的是，那些生产枪械的疯子  发现了你的病情
Unfortunately, you're sick and the gun nazis found out.
他们找到了你的婴儿培育所  认为杀光他们，问题就解决了
They discovered your baby hatchery and, boom, problem solved.
- 杀了婴儿也就相当于杀了你  - 正确
- They kill you by killin' the babies. - Correct.
那我的救星在哪？
So, where's my savior?
哦，天呀，枪！
Oh, my god! Gun!
镇静，镇静
Easy, easy.
你知道我最讨厌什么吗？
You know what i hate most?
- 骗子  - 你他妈的想干什么？
- Liars. - What the hell you doin'?
你和Hammerson是串通好的
You made a deal with hammerson.
- 没有，你疯了  - 是吗？
- No, you're crazy. - Am i?
- 你...  - 你和他穷搞的时候...
- Y... - when you got into bed with him...
他的狗也上了你们的床
you also let his dog up on the mattress.
看看你裤子上的那些狗毛...
Lookin' at those dog hairs on your trousers...
我敢说“老公爵夫人”  肯定喜欢上你了
i'd say old duchess took a likin' to you.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talkin' about.
你的计划留着  你当上总统再说吧，Rutledge
Save the line for when you're in office, rutledge.
如果他还能当总统
If he ever makes it there.
你知道我还讨厌什么吗？
Do you know what else i hate?
伪君子
Hypocrites.
而你是他们当中最大的一个
And you're the biggest one of all.
你能怪他出卖你吗？
Can you blame him for sellin' out?
他要找到婴儿的计划
His operation to find the baby...
从一开始就被破坏了
had been tits up from the get-go.
Rutledge主动找我们，并提出
You see, rutledge called us and he offered us...
一些我们做梦都想不到的好建议
a proposition that we had never dreamed was possible.
以此来交换他的性命
In exchange for his life...
议员答应要维护我们的权力  让我们……
the senator promised to protect our right...
拿着冲锋枪去打猎？
to go deer hunting with an uzi.
哦，拜托  Smith，拜托
Oh, come on, smith. Come on.
枪不会杀人
Guns don't kill people.
它只是帮忙
But they sure help.
退后！
Back off!
退后
Back off.
- 退后，不然我就杀了他  - 哦，不要
- Back off or i'll kill him! - Oh, please.
我没有选择
Pi... i had to do it.
我不想死  我要当总统
I want to live. I am meant to be president.
是吗？你明白那意味着什么？  意味着你的利益高于人民的利益
Yeah? Well, you got what it takes. You put yourself before the people.
我会在其它方面弥补
I can still do good in other areas.
你如何在公众面前改过自新？
How you gonna square it with the public?
宪法里有规定
It is a constitutional right.
退后！退后！
Back off! Get back!
我经常为人民着想
I've come around to their way of thinking.
经常？  他们只听到你说“你好”
Come around? They had you at "hello."
让我给你个建议...
Let me give you a piece of advice...
永远不要相信唯利是图的人  简单明了
never trust the people who stand to profit, plain and simple.
- 他们都是坏人  - 行了，Smith，别逞强了
- They're the bad guys. - Come on, smith, don't be a fool.
游戏结束  你已经掷了骰子，你输了
Go-to guy: The game is over. You rolled the dice, you lost.
放了他，Smith！  你逃不掉的！
Let him go, smith! There's no escape!
也许我真的逃不掉了  不过那个女人和孩子可以
Maybe not for me, but there is for the woman and baby.
如果我杀了Rutledge  就没有人再想去杀他们
If i kill rutledge, no one will need to find them.
她们也就安全了
They'll be saved.
你被暗杀后，Rutledge  人民将愤怒而起
Your assassination, rutledge, will create a public outrage...
你的提议将会得到广大民众的支持
and trigger immense support for your proposals.
出于同情，国会将对你的禁枪议案...
The sympathy vote in the congress will give your anti-gun bills...
给予一致支持
passage by a landslide.
你的遗愿也将实现
Your legacy... will live on.
别开枪！
Don't do it!
那就开枪吧
Then do it.
希望能挽回我的声望…
Let me regain some honor with my...
狗娘养的！
that son of a bitch.
Son of a bitch!
去你妈！
God damn it!
∮有罪犯∮
## It's criminal ##
∮就该有个法律∮
## there ought to be a law ##
∮罪犯∮
## criminal ##
∮该有更多的制裁∮
## there ought to be a whole lot more ##
∮没有付出就没有回报∮
## you get a nothin' for nothin' ##
∮告诉我，你能相信谁？∮
## tell me, who can you trust? ##
∮我们有你想要的∮
## we got what ya want ##
∮而你有欲望∮
## and you got the lust ##
∮如果你要流血∮
## if you want blood ##
∮你会如愿∮
## you got it ##
∮如果你要流血∮
## if you want blood ##
∮你会如愿∮
## you got it ##
∮血流大街∮
## blood on the streets ##
∮血漫石块∮
## blood on the rocks ##
∮血溢下水管道∮
## blood in the gutter ##
∮流尽最后一滴∮
## every last drop ##
∮如果你要流血∮
## you want blood ##
∮你会如愿∮
## you got it ##
∮完全有可能∮
## o positive ##
∮如果你要流血∮
## if you want blood ##
∮你会如愿∮
## you got it ##
别动，英雄先生
don't move, mr. Hero.
现在不方便讲话，亲爱的
Can't talk right now, honey.
我正忙着某事
I'm right in the middle of somethin'.
拜拜
Bye-bye.
别担心，公爵夫人
Don't you worry, duchess.
你不会被扒皮后做成雕像的
This isn't gonna happen to you.
至少几年内都不会
Not for a few years, anyway.
很好，很好
Well, well, well, well, well.
有人变聪明，有人变笨
Somebody gets to be smart, and somebody gets to be dumb.
看来我们终于交换位置了，老兄？
Looks like you and i have finally traded places, huh, sport?
没错，确实
Yes, indeed.
命运的循环
The circle of life.
循环…白痴命运的循环
The circle-a jerk of life.
哦，你总是这样说话
Oh, you have such a way with words.
现在...
Now...
告诉我...
i want you to tell me...
那个女人和小孩在哪？
where the woman and the child are.
告诉我，不然我就让你
Tell me, or i will be forced to cause you...
痛不欲生
considerable agony.
相信我...
Believe me...
没有什么比听你不停的叽哩咕噜  更痛苦了
nothing could be more painful than listenin' to you jabberin' on and on.
我再问一遍
Again, i ask...
那个女人和小孩在哪？
where are the woman and child?
这是你最后一次做这个动作了
That's the last time you'll be doin' that.
只要告诉我，我想要知道的
Just tell me what i wanna hear.
你自己选择什么时候结束
It's your choice when the pain stops.
你为什么要这么做？
Why are you doin' this?
- 都结束了  - 对，很快就会结束了
- It's over. - It shortly will be, yeah.
我真应该好好谢谢你
No, i really should thank you.
因为你，我刚得到一笔大合同
I just got a bigger contract because of you.
你知道吗，我不仅为Hammerson工作
I mean, i wasn't just on hammerson's payroll, you know.
你现在又在咕噜些什么？
What are you babbling on about now?
你真的认为雇佣我的人...
Do you really think the people that employ me...
会因为你杀了议员...
were just gonna bend over and take your little stunt...
就放过你们？
killing the senator?
你不可能掩盖整个事件
There's no way that you can cover up this whole thing.
不可能？你没看新闻吗？
No? Haven't you heard the news?
议员的飞机坠入东河
The senator's plane crashed into the east river.
他们甚至都找不到Rutledge议员的尸体
They haven't been able to find the body of senator rutledge.
所以，一旦我杀了你  还有那个女人...
So, you see, once i silence you and the woman...
就没有人会知道这件事了
the cover-up will be complete.
我再问你一次...
So, once again, i ask you...
女人和小孩在哪？
where are the woman and child?
你知道我会怎么弄断你的手指吗？
You know how i'd break your finger?
我的手下曾告诉我
My boy told me this one.
你会撞我的鼻子
You'd punch me in the nose.
我会踢烂你的屁股
I'd kick you in the ass.
太有趣了
Very amusing.
我再弄断你的拇指
I give that one the ol' thumbs up!
如果我们离开之前  你没赶来怎么办？
What if you don't get to us before we leave?
我知道你的一切
Oh, i know your whole story.
那个在餐馆里疯狂扫射的家伙
That man who went on the shooting spree in the restaurant.
他的枪就是在你继承的枪店里买的
He visited the little gun shop that you inherited from your dad.
我知道你老婆和儿子是怎么死的
I found out how your wife and son were killed.
是你卖给他一把双管散弹猎枪...
You sold him the pair of shotguns...
散弹猎枪
shotguns.
就是那把枪杀了你老婆和儿子
...that killed your own wife and boy.
我不会告诉你任何事情
I'm not telling you... a goddamn thing.
你在哪儿，Smith？
Where are you, smith?
好的，好的
Well, well, well, well, well.
看来我们得用些更厉害的东西了
We're gonna need somethin' a little more invasive.
就这里
That's it.
你的枪真他妈不错  不是吗，Hammerson？
Aren't guns just fucking great, hammerson?
∮拥有绝佳的天赋∮
## Of excellent quality ##
∮我在那儿生活了很多年∮
## i've dwelt there for years ##
∮与我的恐惧斗争∮
## playing with my fears ##
∮过程中有甜蜜、奢华还有性爱∮
## it's tasteful, luxurious, and full of sexuality ##
∮即使还有眼泪∮
## and though there are tears ##
∮我也已经学会了控制∮
## i control them with my gears ##
∮所有的一切∮
## well, all in all ##
∮我必须告诉你∮
## i must tell you ##
## well, i must tell you ##
∮我是如此自豪∮
## i'm so ##
∮我自己的地狱∮
## proud of my private hell ##
嘿
'ey.
我们的神枪手去哪儿了？
Who's a hotshot now, huh?
哦，没错，老兄
Oh, yes, sirree, bob.
认识你真高兴
It certainly has been a pleasure.
但是在我们诀别前...
But before we part ways...
告诉我一件事
tell me one thing.
我完...
I am dead on...
完全猜对了你的身份，是吧？
about who you are, right?
再说一遍？
Say that again?
我说，我完...
I said, i am dead...
停
stop.
这部分你猜对了
That part of it you got right.
你老婆
It's the wife.
嗨，宝贝儿
Hi, honey.
她把我甩了
She's leaving me.
你知道我真正讨厌什么吗？
You know what i really hate?
我真正讨厌的是...
What i really hate...
...手里拿着枪的胆小鬼
...is a pussy with a gun in his hand.
警方今日发现了Rutledge议员的尸体
Investigators discovered the body of senator rutledge today.
FBI声称有关尸体的线索  来自于一个匿名电话
The fbi stated an anonymous tip led them to the remains.
别担心，宝贝
Don't worry, little boy.
妈妈工作的时候也会看着你
Mama will be watching you while she's working.
Oliver
Oliver.
你好
Hello.
你怎么花了这么长时间？
What took you so long?
嘿，抢劫！
All right, this is a robbery!
把抽屉里的钱都交出来
Empty the drawer, all of it.
其他人都别动！
Everyone else, freeze!
谁动我就崩了他的脑袋
Do it or i'll fucking blow your head off!
他说不许动
He said freeze.
包括别再吸你的屁眼了
That means don't even pucker your butthole.
没错，只要别动  谁也不会受到伤害
That's right. No puckering, nobody dies.
全都他妈的别动
So don't fuckin' move.
我们时间很紧，快点！
We're kinda in a rush here, man! Come on!
- 你知道我讨厌什么吗？  - 闭嘴，坐在这上面来，屁眼！
- You know what i hate? - Shut up and sit on this, asshole.
说得好，你听到没！
That's right! You heard him!
-=北理FTP联盟字幕组=-
作品  本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
## Yeah ##
## kickstart my heart, give it a start ##
## ooh, yeah ##
## baby ##
-=BiTUNiON SuBTiTLe GROUP=-
翻译：413413    校对：泠风紊雨
## kickstart my heart, hope it never stops ##
## ooh, yeah ##
## baby, yeah, yeah ##
谢谢欣赏
## skydive naked from an aeroplane ##
## or a lady with a body from outer space ##
## my heart, my heart ##
## kickstart my heart ##
## say i got trouble, trouble in my eyes ##
## i'm just looking for another good time ##
## my heart, my heart ##
## kickstart my heart ##
## yeah, are you ready, girls? ##
## yeah, are you ready now? ##
## ooh, yeah ##
## kickstart my heart ##
## give it a start ##
## ooh, yeah ##
## baby ##
## kickstart my heart, hope it never stops ##
## ooh, yeah, baby ##
## ooh, yeah ##
## kickstart my heart, hope it never stops ##
## baby ##
## ooh, yeah... ##